bakespace.com 2007-01-18

# BakeSpace – Recipe Sharing - Food Tips - Coupons and Social Networking

PRIVACY POLICY 

**Effective July 1, 2006**

**About BakeSpace.com**  
BakeSpace.com is an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through networks of friends. BakeSpace.com members can view each others' profiles, communicate with other members and meet new friends on the service, post and swap recipes, share photos, videos and audio files, post journals/blogs and comments, find tips and answers to cooking and baking questions and search local events. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. BakeSpace.com members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

BakeSpace.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at privacy@BakeSpace.com.

**Information Collection and Use by BakeSpace.com**   
BakeSpace.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the BakeSpace.com service. BakeSpace.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, recipes, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

BakeSpace.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the BakeSpace.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join BakeSpace.com, to add users to members' friends' networks, listed as user in chat room, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications and chat room ID, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on BakeSpace.com with each other through the BakeSpace.com service, without disclosing their email addresses, unless listed in a chat room. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members outside their first degree network.  If you do not with to publish your last name to your first degree network, after you sign up for service you can delete your last name in your account settings. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, BakeSpace.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, any item in one’s profile that you have in common with another member and schools and/or, but not limited to, companies where users may have attended or worked.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.  BakeSpace will only email you from a corporate account email. 

From time to time, BakeSpace.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on BakeSpace.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**  
BakeSpace members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. BakeSpace.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations.  BakeSpace.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from BakeSpace.com may contact BakeSpace.com to request the removal of their information from our database. 

BakeSpace members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal BakeSpace address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.  
You may prevent BakeSpace.com email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by un-checking the box that reads “Send me e-mail notification about invitations, friend requests and messages in my Inbox” at the bottom of your account page. 

**Use of Cookies**  
BakeSpace.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from BakeSpace.com in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that BakeSpace allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the BakeSpace Privacy Policy. 

**Links**   
BakeSpace.com contains links to sites. BakeSpace.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on BakeSpace.com. 

**Profile, **Blogs, Recipes, Pantry, Message Boards, Classifieds, Chat Rooms and Public Forums****   
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to your profile, Blogs, Recipes, Panty Messages, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**  
BakeSpace.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by BakeSpace.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BakeSpace.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Security**  
BakeSpace.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords BakeSpace.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on BakeSpace.com, please contact us a privacy@BakeSpace.com 

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information BakeSpace.com Collects**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, BakeSpace will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by BakeSpace.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the BakeSpace.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. BakeSpace reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of BakeSpace or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@BakeSpace.com or PO BOX 18297, Beverly Hills, CA 90209.
